OK
Okay.
这次的作业有点大
Now for the big quiz.
在预报细节界面中使用CursorLoader
Implement the details view
using a CursorLoader.
我们刚刚在ForecastFragment中使用了CursorLoader
We've just implemented a CursorLoader
for forecast fragment.
如果你不确定从哪儿开始的话
So if you're unsure where to start,
start with the same steps we used for
照着ForecastFragment的步骤做
forecast fragment.
你可以用相同的Utility中的函数
You can use the same
utility functions and
甚至ForecastFragment中相同的格式化函数
even the same format that we
used in forecast fragment
来格式化设置到预报细节视图的字符串
to help you format the string that
you will set into the detail view.
别忘了使用projection
Consider taking
advantage of projections.
有点复杂的部分是要确保完成时
The trickiest part of all this is
making sure that your sharing function
你的分享功能还能正常运行
is still working when you're all done.
不过别太担心
But don't worry too much about that.
重要的是要理解CursorLoader是怎么工作的
The important thing is to
understand how CursorLoaders work.
如果你真的想看看分享部分是怎么做的，看下解答
Look at the solution if you really
want to see how sharing is done.
如果你对这部分不怎么清楚的话
If you're at all confused
about how sharing is done,
just look at the solution.